Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Sound recordings, 242013
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985; 197226
    - Iggy My Father's Place Nov. 4, 1979;John Cale Sabotage/Live, ID: 213.0407; 216823 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0407)
      Side B: (Cont'd), China Girl/ Cale: Mercenaries (Ready For War), Baby You Know, Evidence, Dr. Mudd, Only Time Will Tell, Sabotage
    - Iggy & the Stooges, 1969; ID: 213.0408; 216824 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0408)
      Side A: I Wanna Be Your Dog, No Fun, Real Cool Time, Not Right, Little Doll, Down on the Street, Loose, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1970
      Side B: Funhouse, Search & Destroy, Your Pretty Face is Going to Hell, Raw Power, Shake Appeal, Death Trip
    - Iggy Pop Live March 18th 1977, March 18, 1977; ID: 213.0409; 216825 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0409)
      Side A: Raw Power, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1969, Turn Blue, Funtime, Gimmie Danger, No Fun, Search & Destroy, I Wanna Be Your Dog
      Side B: Tonight, Some Weird Sin, China Girl
      Container Annotation: Iggy w/ P.S. Group - 96 Tears
    - The Feelies Dec 14, 1977 CBGB, December 14, 1977; ID: 213.0410; 216826 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0410)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Clean Girl, Work, [Track Unknown], Little Red Book, Moscow Night, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy Next Door, Original Love/Sin, Third Uncle, The Thin Line, [Track Unknown], Work, Moscow Night, Slippin
    - Some Jams NYC 78 Speed, 1978; ID: 213.0411; 216885 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0411)
      Side A: Jam: Richard Lloyd and the Feelies Max's Kansas City NYC / 19 Jan 78 Side 1 of 2 (45:54)
      Side B: Side 2 of 2 Patti Smith Group, Richard Lloyd, Richard Hell "My Generation" CBGBs II / NYC 31 Dec 77, 1 Jan 78 (8:52)// Hurram Jam / Hurrahs NYC / 4 Sept 78 John Cale, Chris Spedding, T. Taliafero Drummer (20:47)
      Container Annotation: © Performances and All Original Material Copyright 1978 By the Artists. All Commercial Rights Retained
    - Richard & Linda Thompson Sept 7th Round House London, undated; ID: 213.0412; 216910 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0412)
      Contents: (Original text crossed out, See Container Annotation for Original Text)
      Side A: I Want to See the Bright Lites T'Nite+, Hard Luck Stories(), My Dreams Have Withered and Died*, Streets of Paradise(), Old Woman Tossed Up in a Blanket/Shepards Hey/Bean Setting/Shooting[], A Heart Needs a Home*, Together Again, Everything You Do*
      Side B: Jet Plane in a Rocking Chair(), Never Again*, For Shame of Doing Wrong(), Hokey Pokey+, Looking for You*/Steeleye Span (T.V.) Ballad of Robin Hood, One Misty Musty Morn, Spotted Cow
      Note: () - From "Pour Down Like Silver"; * - NOT SURE; + - TITLE SONGS FROM 1st and 2nd Album; []Medley from "Morrison";- Buck Owens Tune. Drums - Davis [Maptaoks]; Bass - Pat Donaldson; J- Kirkpatrick
      Container Annotation: Advertising Age 7th Annual Idea Workshop Consumer Direct Mail
    - Iggy Pop Oct 31, '79 Palladium, October 31, 1979; ID: 213.0414; 216912 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0414)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, [Track Unknown], I'm Loose, Dog Food, New Values, T.V. Eye, Sixteen, Pretty Face Going to Hell, Play It Safe
      Side B: Funtime, [Track Unknown], I Wanna Be Your Dog, China Girl, One For My Baby An' One Forthe Road, No Fun, Five Foot One, [Track Unknown]
    - MC5 Lester Bangs Saginaw Auditorium, Demo, January 1, 1970; ID: 213.0414; 216913 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0414)
      Side A: Ramblin Rose, Human Being Lawnmower, Tonight, Rocket Reducer #62, It's a Man's World, Teenage Lust, Looking at You, Five of Love, Shakin' Street, Starship-->, Kickout the Jams
      Side B: I Sold My Babe, Let it Blurt
      Container Annotation: [J.D. Dougherty] - Drums, Bob [Quinel] - Guitar
    - Madness TR3, Sunday Nov 25 '79, November 25, 1979; ID: 213.0415; 216915 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0415)
    - B-52's, Talking Heads, Aug 16. '79 Central Park, August 16, 1979; ID: 213.0416; 216916 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0416)
      Side A: Planet Claire, Big Country
      Side B: Warning Sign, Building On Fire, Book I Read, Paper, [Track Unknown], Stay Hungry, [Track Unknown]
    - Talking Heads Live, Assorted Dates, 1975-1976; ID: 213.0417; 216917 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0417)
      Side A: Girls Wanna Be w/ the Girls, With Our Love, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Love (cut), Building on Fire, Artist's Only, Warning Sign, No Compassion, Artists Only, First Week/Last Week, ...With Our Love
      Side B: Love is Like a Building on Fire, Who is it?, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, Book I Read, Don't Worry About Gov't, Psycho Killer, Building On Fire, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, Stay Hungry, [Track Unknown], 96 Tears
      Container Annotation: Tracks 1-8: Live at CBGB July 18, 1975; Tracks 9-14: Live at Max's May 19, 1976; Tracks 15-22: Live at Max's Oct 8th, 1976; Tracks 23-25 Live at CBGB Jan 25, 1976
    - Talking Heads CBGB Sunday August 28th 1977. "Voidoids Village Gate Friday August 26th 77" (crossed out), August 28, 1977; ID: 213.0418; 216935 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0418)
      Side A: Love-->Building on Fire, Love Comes to Town, Don't Worry About the Gov't, Take Me to the River, Don't Take My Love Away, Pulled Up, No Compassion
      Side B: Love Comes to Town, With Our Love, Girls w/ Girls, Tentative Decisions, Thank You For --> Angel, Who is it?, I'm Not In Love, Love-->Building, Psycho Killer, Love is All Around
    - Talking Heads CBGB 3-Piece Band, 1976, ID: 213.0419; 216936 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0419)
      Side A: Artists Only, ...Book I Read, Happy Day, Don't Worry...Government, Thank you...an Angel, Last Week...Carefree, Buildings on Fire, New Feeling, I'm Not In Love, Girls Want 2 B w/ tha Goils!!!
      Side B: With Our Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That!!!, Psycho Killa, Tentative Decisions, Stay Hungry, Warning Sign, Who Is It?, Love is All Around, 1-2-3-Red Light
    - Early TV Video Dub Spring 74?/Talking Heads Summer 75 Video Dub, One Plus One, 1974-1976; ID: 213.0420; 216937 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0420)
      Contents: Merry Christmas + Cassette Luv to Peter
      Side A: Double Exposure, Change Your Channel, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Venus de Milo, [Track Unknown], Sympathy for the Devil
      Side B: Girls Wanna Be w/ the Girls, With Our Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That, I'm Not In Love, Psycho Killer, Warning Sign, Pablo Picasso*, Oh Oh I Love Her So (Blondie)
      Container Annotation: T.V. Early 1974 w/ R. Hell - bass, vocal; Live at CBGB's Summer 1975 (Aug 15th), *10/9/76
    - Blondie CBGB July 18, 1975, CBGB Aug 1975, CBGB May 7, 1978, 1975, 1978; ID: 213.0421; 216938 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0421)
      Side A: Little Girl Lies, In the Flesh, Moonlight, Drive, Charlotte Harlot, Platinum Blonde, Man Overboard, Little Girl Lies, In the Still of the Night, Femme Fatale, Sweet Lulabye
      Side B: Sister Midnight, Denise
    - Nervus Rex May 26 Max's/B-52's June 1 '78 CBGB, 1978; ID: 213.0422; 216939 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0422)
      Side A: Index, I Love You or Whatever, Love Affair, Fun w/ Numbers, No Regrets, Sort of, Rachel in the Ruins [?], Don't Look at Me That Way/She Came From Planet, Hero Worship, 52 Girls, Devin in My Car
      Side B: Downtown, Rock Lobster, Hero Worship, 52-Girls, Devils in My Car, Downtown, Lava, Runnin Around
    - B-52's Sat Late Sept 23, 1978 CBGB/Hurrah Oct 1 '78, ID: 213.0423; 216940 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0423)
      Side A: 52 Girls, Hero Worship, Devil's in my Car, Downtown, Moon in the Sky, Dance, Rock Lobster, Runnin' Around
      Side B: Planet Cloud, Hero Worship, 52 Girls, Devil's in my Car, Downtown, [Track Unknown], Lava, Moon in the Sky..., [Track Unknown]
    - B-52's September 21, 1978 CBGB, ID: 213.0424; 217025 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0424)
      Side A: She Came From Planet Cloud, Dance, Runnin' Around, Downtown, Lava, There's a Moon, Strobe Light, Rock Lobster
      Side B: 52 Girls, Hero Worship, devin's in My Car, Downtown, Running Around, Dance, Rock Lobster, Strobe Light
    - Heartbreakers ala Book, undated; ID: 213.0425; 217035 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0425)
    - JT [Thunders], unknown; ID: 213.0426; 217036 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0426)
    - The Cramps Live June 10th 1977, Nov 4th CBGB, Dec 13, 1978, 1977-1978; ID: 213.0427; 217037 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0427)
      Side A: The Way I Walk, Love Me, Domino, What's Behind the Mask, Don't Eat Stuff off the Sidewalk, Teenage Werewolf, Sunglasses After Dark, I Put You in My TV Set, Human Fly, [Strinne] Love Me, Domino, What's Behind the Mask
      Side B: Jungle Hop, Teenage Werewolf, Sunglasses After Dark, I'm Cramped, T.V. Set, Surfin' Bird, Human Fly, What Color Panties Are Ya Wearing?, Daddy Drives a UFO
    - DEVO Max's 5-25-77, A Grape Tape, Plus Iggy 1, May 25, 1977; ID: 213.0428; 217038 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0428)
      Side A: Human Race, Social Fools, Be Stiff, Too Much Paranoias, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Spud Boy, Sloppy, Satisfaction, Blockhead, Soo Bawlz, Penetration in the Centerfold
      Side B: Mongoloid, Gut Feeling, Jocko Homo, Come Back Johnny, Words Get Stuck in My Throat, [Track Unknown], That's How Strong My Love Is-->FAME, I Wanna Be Your Dog
    - Erasers/Feelies/Cramps/CBGBS/Live/NYC 77/78, 1977-1978; ID: 213.0429; 217039 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0429)
      Contents: CBGBs/LIVE/NEW YORK CITY
      Side A (The Erasers 29 May 77/Set 2 (28:16); The Feelies 29 May 77/Set1 Side 1 of 2 (16:59)): Jody, No Fun, Funtime, Come out in the Streets, Marc in Leather, Everybody's Got a Dog, I Don't Love Anyone, Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La
      Side B (The Feelies (Cont) Side 2 of 2 (12:49); The Cramps 19 Feb 78/Set 2 (29:44)): I'm a Believer, Original Love, Human Fly, Love Me, What's Behind the Mask, Jungle Hop, Teenage Werewolf, Daddy, Drives a UFO, Strycnine, What Color Panties? Hanky Panky, Surfin Bird
      Container Annotation: Performances and All Material Copyright 1977 and 1978 by the Artists. All Commercial Rights Reserved.
    - Cramps 8-18-79 WPIX Dolby/Undertones 9-20-79 Palladium, 1979; ID: 213.0430; 217040 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0430)
      Side A: CRAMPS 8-18-79 11:03-11:43pm WPIX
      Side B: True Confessions, Girls Don't Like It, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Billy's Third, [Track Unknown], Jump Boys
    - Contortions/Cramps CBGB Fri April 14th 1978 late show, April 14, 1978; ID: 213.0431; 217262 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0431)
      Side A: My Infatuation, I Got a Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed, Throw Me Away, Flip Your Face, Jaded But So in Love
      Side B: The Way I Walk, Love Me, Jungle Hop, Human Fly, [S+rec], I'm Cramped, Hanky Panky
    - Hip Hop Junkies Vol. IV, Puffin On a Blunt!, Alex Baby: Straight Outta Ronin! In Tha Mix!, undated; ID: 213.0432; 217271 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0432)
      Side A: Alex Baby
      Side B: "How High?"
    - Rocket From the Tombs '75 w/ Peter Laughner, undated; ID: 213.0433; 217509 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0433)
      Sides A and B: Intro, I'm 18
    - Feelies September 78 - Max's Sept 1, 1978 Early/Max's Sept 2, 1978 Early, September 1978; ID: 213.0434; 217510 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0434)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights,... Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows--> Crazy Rhythms --> Well Alright
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, ...Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl-->Original Love, Raised Eyebrows-->Crazy Rhythms, Well Alright
    - Sid Vicious Max's Sept 8, 1978 w/ Mick Jones, J. Nolan, A. Kane & S. Doir, September 8, 1978; ID: 213.0435; 217512 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0435)
      Side A: DEVO 10-14-78, Search and Destroy, I Wanna Be Your Dog, Pushin & Shovin', Something Else, Belsen was a Gas, Steppin Stone, Chinese Rocks, My Way, [Track Unknown]
      Container Annotation: Side A: 1, 2, 5, 3/Side B: 3 cont'd, 4,6,7,9
    - Devo 76 Studio Demos - Talking Heads Demos, 1976; ID: 213.0436; 217513 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0436)
      Side A: (Devo) Sloppy, Blockhead, Uncontrollable Urge, Secret Agent Man, Clock-Out, Auto Mowdown, Smart Patrol, Mechanical Man, Be Stiff, Bottled Up/ (Talking Heads) First Week/Last Week..., Artists Only, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That
      Side B: New Feeling*, Book I Read*, Not in Love*, Love-->Building, Book I Read, I'm Not in Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That
      Container Annotation: *Live
    - Devo Mabuhay Tapes, Aug 3, '77, Sept 12, '77, 1977; ID: 213.0437; 217514 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0437)
      Side A: Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Smart Patrol/Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, Jocko Homo, Clock Out
      Side B: Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Jocko Homo, Smart Patrol-Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, The Words Get Stuck in My Throat
    - Undertones Hurrah Sept 23 '79 plus WPIX, September 23, 1979; ID: 213.0438; 217511 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0438)
      Side A: Here Comes the Summer
    - Deadline CBGB Nov 29th, 1980/Elodie Lawton [Wednesday] March 4th 1981 Max's, November 29, 1980, March 4, 1981; ID: 213.0439; 217515 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0439)
      Contents: Unknown
    - Cuban Heels July 26th 1977 CBGB/Nervus Rex Tuesday October 18 1977 CBGB, ID: 213.0440; 217516 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0440)
      Side A: Come Out in the Streets, Time To Wake Up, I Remember, [Track Unknown], Joey Run Run, [Track Unknown], California, Secret Agent
      Side B: (Fun with numbers*), Third Word, Duplicate, Love Affair, Index, I Love You or Whatever, [Track Unknown], 1250, Rachel in Ruins Again, December Pledge
      Container Annotation: *Soundcheck, Miriam, Trixie, [Sham]
    - Talking Heads Entermedia Theater August 10, 1978, ID: 213.0441; 217553 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0441)
      Side A: No Compassion, Warning Sign, Book I Read, Girls w/ the Girls, Love Comes to Town, With Our Love, Love--> Building
      Side B: I Found a Job, Electricity, Big Country, Pulled Up
    - Talking Heads 3/13/76, Talking Heads Dec 7th, 1975 CBGB Set I, 1975-1976; ID: 213.0442; 217554 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0442)
      Sides A and B: (Talking Heads March 13, 1976) Love is All Around; 1,2,3, Redlight; 96 Tears/(December 7th 1975), Girls Wanna Be with the Girls, First Week/Last Week, Artists Only, Building on Fire, With Our Love, Warning Sign II, Psycho Killer, Tentative Decisions, I Wanna Live, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That, I'm Not in Love, Stay Hungry, Girls w/Girls (crossed out), With Our Love (crossed out), I Wish You Wouldn't Say That (crossed out), So in Love
    - Talking Heads Central Park '80 Dr. Pepper, August 27, 1980; ID: 213.0443; 217555 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0443)
      Side A: Psycho Killer, Warning Sign, Stay Hungry, Cities, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Crosseyed & Painless, Life During Wartime, Take Me to the River, [Track Unknown]
    - Talking Heads July 29, 1976 CBGB, STEREO Set #1/Talking Heads Set #2, ID: 213.0444; 217556 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0444)
      Side A: Artists Only ([gone]), Don't Worry About Gov't, Love is All Around, Building on Fire, Who is it?, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, ...With Our Love, Book I Read
      Side B: Girls w/ Girls, Happy Feeling, Stay Hungry, New Feeling, I'm Not in Love, Warning Sign
    - Iggy Pop Suckcess Tour, Hunt & Tony Sales, A Grape Tape, October 6, 1977; ID: 213.0445; 217557 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0445)
      Side A: Sixteen, Lust for Life, Neighborhood Threat, The Passenger, I Gotta Right
      Side B: Some Weird Sin, Nightclubbin, Raw Power, That's How Strong My Love Is
    - Heads cont'd, undated; ID: 213.0446; 217558 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0446)
      Side A: Artists Only, Psycho Killer, Life During Wartime, Take Me to the River, No Compas[sion], Designed to Kill, Throw Me Away
    - Talking Heads T.V. Aug 3 Last show with Lloyd -almost-Thanks/Roxy Music Oct 18th, undated; ID: 213.0447; 217559 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0447)
      Side A (Talking Heads, TV 8/3): Girls Wanna Be With Girls, With Our Love, Psycho Killer, Tentative Decision/(T.V.) Fire Engine, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel
      Side B (Roxy Music): Street Life, Remake/ReModel, Do the Strand, Re-Make, Editions of You, Do the Strand, -encores-, Thrill of it All, Hard Rains Gonna Fall
    - Stooges Live '74, 1974; ID: 213.0448; 217560 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0448)
      Side A: Raw Power, Rich bitch, Wet My Bed, I Got Nothin', Cock in My Pocket, Search & Destroy, Gimmie Danger
      Side B: I Got Nothin'
    - MTV EMA 30 Sec 1st Demo, undated; ID: 213.0449; 217561 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0449)
    - New York Dolls, Montreal, Canada 27.9.74, September 27, 1974; ID: 213.0450; 217562 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0450)
      Side A: Lookin For A Kiss, Who Are the Mystery Girls, Something Else, Pills, Give Her A Great Big Kiss, Subway, It's Too Late
      Side B: Trash, Bad Girl, Chatterbox, Puss in Boots, Stranded in the Jungle
    - Newsrap, undated; ID: 213.0451; 217563 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0451)
      Side A: "Newsrap" - M.T.V; Rough Guide Demo 1) with Drumloop 2) without Drumloop, 130 B.P.M.
      Container Annotation: Dan Denovan 289.3484
    - MTV Ident: Clive Walley Demo for Peter Dougherty, undated; ID: 213.0452; 218323 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0452)
    - MTV Rough Demo, undated; ID: 213.0453; 217564 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0453)
      Sides A and B: MTV Awards 60 Secs, MTV Awards 30 Secs, For Demo Only, Barry Adamson
    - VH1 15/6/94, June 15, 1994; ID: 213.0454; 217565 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0454)
      Contents: VH1 Revised Ideas
      Sides A and B: Morning - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Afternoon - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Evening 1 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Evening 2 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Late Nite 1 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Late Nite 2 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs
      Container Annotation: © Picture Sounds Publishing 1994
      Tape Length: 50 minutes
    - Suicide Mudd Feb 6, 1979, ID: 213.0455; 217597 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0455)
      Side A: Lloyd Mud Jan 5, 1979 encore-late/Suicide Mud Feb 6, 1979
    - Suicide 57 Club Irving Plaza Sat. Jul 21 '79/CBGB 8-21-80, July 21, 1979/ August 21, 1980; ID: 213.0456; 217598 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0456)
      Sides A and B: Rocket U.S.A., Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Radiation, Harlem
    - Suicide Alan/with, Max's April 13 '79, Max's June 16, '80 w/ Wiseguys, Max's Nov 23 '80 w/ [Kramer], 1979-1980; ID: 213.0457; 217599 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0457)
      Side A: Touch Me, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Four Horsemen, Rocket U.S.A. Sweetheart
    - Suicide Aug 25 '78 Max's (one set)/Judy Nylon Aug 27 '78 Max's (one set) w/ P. Pat Place, August 1978; ID: 213.0458; 217600 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0458)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Cheree, Mr. Ray, Johnny, Harlem
      Side B: Unknown
    - Contortions Max's 10/12/78 only set/T.J. & Jerks Nov 4 '78 only set CBGB/Suicide Nov 4 '78 2nd Set CBGB. Dead Boys WPIX Oct 28 1978, ID: 213.0459; 217601 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0459)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Disposable You, Dish it Out, [Track Unknown], Designed to Kill (x), [Track Unknown], Almost Black, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Mr. Ray, Four Horsemen, 96 Tears, Harlem
    - Suicide Hurrah Sept 27 1978/Suicide Nov 1978 CBGB Nov. 3 1978 2nd set Nov. 4 1978 1st set, ID: 213.0460; 217606 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0460)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Mr. Ray, Keep Your Dreams, Las Vegas, [Track Unknown], 96 Tears, Harlem
      Side B: Dance, Las Vegas, 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Ride, Johnny, I Remember, Ghost Rider
    - Suicide CBGB 2/4/78, Max's 1/13/78/Contortions late show CBGB 2/4/78, 1978; ID: 213.0461; 217607 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0461)
      Side A: Dance, 96 Tears, Rocket U.S.A., Frankie, Dance, 96 Tears, Frankie
      Side B: I Don't Wanna Be Happy, My Infatuatino, Love Twice Removed, I'm Not a Bedroom Athlete, Jaded But So in Love, Roving Eye, Enjoy Yourself, Contort Yourself, Throw Me Away
    - The Cult 20 Oct '86, October 20, 1986; ID: 213.0462; 217608 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0462)
      Side A: Love Removal Machine, Wild Flower, Peace Dog, Aphrodisiac Jacket, Electric Ocean, Bad Fun
      Side B: Conquistador, Zap City, Love Trooper, Outlaw, Groove Co.
    - Doors LIVE Matrix San Francisco '67/ Roundhouse London '68, 1967-1968; ID: 213.0463; 217609 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0463)
      Side A: People Are Strange, Whiskey Bar, Crystal Ship, Unhappy Girl, Moonlight Drive, Summer's Almost Gone, 20th Century Fox, Backdoor Man, My Eyes Have Seen You, Soul Kitchen, Get Out of My Life Woman
      Side B: Light My Fire, Break on Thru, Five to One, The End, When the Music's Over
    - Suicide March 31 CBGB 2 sets/April 1 '78 one set/& Feb 4, 77 CBGB, 1977-1978; ID: 213.0464; 217610 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0464)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Speed Queen, Harlem, Dance, Ghost Rider, 96 Tears, Frankie
      Side B: Rocket USA, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Frankie, 96 Tears/Rocket USA, Jesus
    - Big Youth/Clash/[Tramps] Sept 30 1980, September 30, 1980; ID: 213.0465; 217611 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0465)
      Side A: unknown
      Side B: Mag 7, Equalize, Call Up, Lose This Skin, Lightning, Up In Heaven, [Kingston] Advice, Mensforth Hill
    - Dread at the Control #2, undated; ID: 213.0335; 199249 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0335)
    - Voidoids [Rev Kitchen] CBGB Oct 6 '77, October 6, 1977; ID: 213.0466; 217612 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0466)
      Sides A and B: Liars, Lose, Blank, Ventilator, Betrayal, Walkin'
    - Fleshtones, Zantees, Communists: Club 57 and Artists Space, April 7, 1978; May 2, 1978; ID: 213.0467; 231665 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0467)
    - The Fury Sound, undated; ID: 213.0468; 231666 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0468)
    - Outer Limits: My Father's Place, June 7th, 1976; ID: 213.0469; 231667 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0469)
    - Patti Smith - Elgin, July 30, 1977; ID: 213.0470; 231668 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0470)
    - Patti Smith Live at the Other End, June 29, 1975; ID: 213.0471; 231669 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0471)
    - Raincoats TR3, May 16, 1980; ID: 213.0472; 231670 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0472)
    - Rap Party Riz, March 11, 1981; ID: 213.0473; 231671 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0473)
    - Shatki with J McLaughlin, June 28, 1976; ID: 213.0474; 231672 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0474)
    - Television Live CBGB, May 26, 1976; ID: 213.0475; 231673 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0475)
    - Television Live CBGB, January 23, 1976; ID: 213.0476; 231674 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0476)
    - Television Live CBGB, March 11, 1976; ID: 213.0477; 231675 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0477)
    - Wailers Live, June 18, 1975; ID: 213.0478; 231676 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0478)
    - Wailers Live at the Beacon Theatre, May 7, 1976; ID: 213.0479; 231677 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0479)
- Series II: Video recordings / Film, 242014
  - Subseries A: Video Works, 218297
    - Stevie Wonder Tape 3, undated; ID: 213.0354; 199589 (Box 9, Case 213.0354)
      Content: Crew talking after performance. Stevie Wonder does not appear on the disc.
      Format: 8mm Videocassette
      Access DVD available for researchers by appointment only.
    - [Untitled Compilation Tape], undated; ID: 213.0355; 199590 (Box 9, Case 213.0355)
      Contents (Based on Container Annotation):
      Music Box, Coach to Paris, French T.V., Coach to Gig, Hippadrome Pre-Show, Island Special -U2, Bowie-->, Doherty's Donegal, [Malin] Head, British TV Fashion Show, Wilson's House, Tyrone Self Interview, Pontoon-John
    - Nelson George-Black Radio/Declaration of Independents, undated; ID: 213.0356; 199591 (Box 9, Case 213.0356)
    - J.A. [Jefferson Airplane] Dick Cavett, Filmore Movie I, undated; ID: 213.0357; 199592 (Box 9, Case 213.0357)
    - Videos, undated; ID: 213.0358; 199594 (Box 9, Case 213.0358)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation):
      Joe Strummer "Gangsville", Suicide "Surrender" "Dominic", Capt Beefheart "Ice Cream For Crows", Murphy Law "Panty Raid", Bad Brains, Red Hot Chili "[white out] Ground", Bootsie!
    - Beastie Boy Guest V.J. Jan '87 Segments Promos, January 1987; ID: 213.0359; 199595 (Box 9, Case 213.0359)